[
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of the doctor in network programming?",
        "answer": "mohannad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mention the number of the university hall where the networking course is taught",
        "answer": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the programming language that we learned at the beginning of the course?",
        "answer": "python"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the function of conditions in language?",
        "answer": "if"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it possible to delete an item from a list in the language?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "WWhat is the outcome of the process 4*4+2 ?",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the name of the verification function at the beginning of a word",
        "answer": "startswith()"
    },
    {
        "question": "Indicate according to the Gregorian calendar the last date for submitting the homework",
        "answer": "27/5/2024"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the suffix of a Python file named 'almekdad'?",
        "answer": ".py"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the square root of 64?",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Would you benefit from the course?",
        "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the type of variable that contains the following value: 100 ",
        "answer": "integer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the type of variable that contains the following value: almekdad ",
        "answer": "string"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the type of variable that contains the following value: [1,5,222] ",
        "answer": "list"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the type of variable that contains the following value: (1,2) ",
        "answer": "set"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output of the instruction print('almekdad mohannad')",
        "answer": "almekdadmohannad"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 1+1 ?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 3%3 ?",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 2*2*2 ?",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is 2/2 ?",
        "answer": "1"
    }
]